{
    "id": "e51663e8e3ff46bdbdad122e09b5770c",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs With Set",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The children were ....................... going to the movies, but the rain played spoilsport.",
            "description": "When you are set on doing something, you believe that it will happen. ",
            "answers": [
                "set to",
                "set about",
                "set on"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The girl didn't take even five minutes to ......................... the train set.",
            "description": "To set up something is to put together. ",
            "answers": [
                "set out",
                "set up",
                "set on"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "What sets him ................... from his colleagues is his commitment to his work.",
            "description": "Set apart = make something or someone distinct from others.",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "off",
                "apart"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She set ................. the novel and started doing her homework.",
            "description": "To set something aside is to put it to the side because you don't want to use it at the moment.",
            "answers": [
                "off",
                "apart",
                "aside"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She has faced many ................... in life.",
            "description": "Setback is written as one word. A setback is an unfavorable situation that hinders your progress.",
            "answers": [
                "set offs",
                "set backs",
                "setbacks"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He set the stereo ................... on the table.",
            "description": "To set something down is to put it down.",
            "answers": [
                "down",
                "out",
                "aside"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Winter has set ..................",
            "description": "When a season sets in, it begins to happen.",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "up",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Three months after quitting the job, remorse set ...............",
            "description": "When feelings set in, they begin to be felt.",
            "answers": [
                "off",
                "out",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "We set .................... on our voyage in the morning.",
            "description": "To set off is to begin a journey.",
            "answers": [
                "off",
                "up",
                "down"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The decision to build a dam in the ecologically sensitive region set ................... a wave of protests.",
            "description": "To set off an event is to trigger it.",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "off",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The merchant set .................... on his journey in the morning.",
            "description": "To set out on a journey is to start it. Set off also means the same. ",
            "answers": [
                "off",
                "out",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "They set .................... the tent in a couple of minutes.",
            "description": "Set up means establish. ",
            "answers": [
                "down",
                "out",
                "off",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        }
    ]
}